Hallelujah!
Are you there?
I want to believe you have settled your account.
The principle in The SCOAN is what we believe in the Bible.
If you have not settled your account let us settle it now, it's not too late.
How many of you are still holding grudges, holding offence?
Whether right or wrong, you have no right to hold offence.
One thing we must know: an offence opens the door to satan.
Tell your neighbour.
[Offence opens the door to satan.]
Satan is looking for a way of getting you.
We Christians believe that, ... "I have stopped smoking, lying, going to night-clubs. Now I live a righteous life."
But you are still claiming your right, when someone accused you - you hold an offence against that person.
An offence opens the door to satan.
You keep saying, "What is the cause of my problem? I have not been smoking, and doing other things.
I have been living a righteous life. Why this setback? Why this trouble? Why nightmare? Why sickness?"
An offence opens the door to demons.
You know what satan brings when he comes to your life;
he brings affliction, depression, poverty, hardship, crisis, all what you are facing now - the situation you are in.
An offence opens the door to satan.
Tell your neighbour again.
[An offence opens the door to satan.]
Again.
When you hold offence, whether you are right or wrong;
when you hold a grudge against a brother, you have already grieved the Holy Spirit
because you are not allowed to hold an offence, whether you are wrong or right.
You know, we Christians are always right - that is our principle.
We are right while others are wrong.
You lie against me, and you hold an offence against him; you are grieving the Holy Spirit.
Then, you allow satan.
Are you with me?
Viewers all over the world, wherever you are; whatever position you are in – listen to me.
An offence opens the door to satan and you know what satan brings when he comes -
disease, situation, depression – just name all those foolish things
that is the work of satan; he is synonymous with these.
When you talk of sickness, satan is synonymous – he gives birth to them.
An offence opens the door.
Whether you are right or wrong, you have no right to hold an offence.
When you hold a grudge against a brother, you have already grieved God Himself.
You have to be free; when your spirit is free, it can contact the Spirit of God.
A free spirit contacts the Spirit of God – is sensitive to the Spirit of God.
It is time now, before we begin to pray, it is time for you and me...
This is why I'm asking you, "Have you settled your account?"
This is what the Bible means by forgive me as I have forgiven those who what?
Forgive me as I have what?
This is what the Bible is talking about.
Forgive me as I have forgiven those who sin against me.
Have you?
You have to forgive; if you forgive, you hold no offence – you let offence go.
Right now, open your lips and begin to "fire-on".
Remember, you need restitution.
When you leave here just make a call.
A phone call can settle many of your cases.
Right now, prayer.
Ask God to give you the grace.
Give me enablement Lord, to forgive those who have wronged me.
Lord Jesus, give me enablement.
Real love forgets wrongs so that there will be hope for the future.
The reason why you have to forget and love is that a servant today can be a leader tomorrow.
Someone you call a murderer today, your enemy today, can be your saviour tomorrow.
Your greatest enemy can be your saviour tomorrow or the saviour of your children.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Tomorrow is a mystery.
Since tomorrow is a mystery, we don't know what will happen next,
we have to be very careful today so that we will not annoy, offend tomorrow.
Tell your neighbour, "Tomorrow is a mystery."
[Tomorrow is a mystery.]
Since I don’t know what will happen tomorrow,
[Since I don’t know what will happen tomorrow,]
I don’t want to offend tomorrow.
[I don’t want to offend tomorrow.]
You can offend tomorrow by today.
What you are doing today can offend tomorrow; what you are doing today can give favour tomorrow.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Yes, you cannot just explain tomorrow because God is tomorrow and the future.
Since you don’t know tomorrow, today you have to be very careful.
Be very very careful.
God does as He wills.
He can take what is unlikely to the palace and undeserved one would be there.
He does as He wills.
Let us be very very careful.
This is why you shouldn't judge your children by their character now.
The worst of your children can be the king tomorrow, the saviour of the family tomorrow.
Don't judge them be their attitude or character; continue to press on to changed them.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
I want to speak to every challenge.
We know satan is behind your challenges.
Satan is the cause of challenges.
Satan is responsible for whatever challenges you have because satan is synonymous with challenges.
I speak to every challenge in your life and I command them to leave, in Jesus' name.
You demon, I speak to you wherever you are in their lives -
be it their career,
be it their destiny,
be it their finances,
be it their business – out, in Jesus' name.
I speak to you demon, I command you to leave them, in the name of Jesus.
Say, "Demon, leave me, in the name of Jesus."
Remember, every knee shall bow.
"Knees" means, demons must bow.
Every tongue shall confess Jesus.
Demons must listen to the voice of God.
I say to you, you demon – out, in Jesus' name!
You satan – out, in Jesus' name!
Command them out, in Jesus' name.
The SCOAN Sunday Service
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
Overflow Congregation
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I just want you to give me your heart and let me pray for you.
It means, hear me with all your heart - this is what I mean.
Let me offer a prayer.
With all your heart you can pray with me in the Spirit.
Just say "amen" in the Spirit.
Pray with me in the Spirit.
Right now, are you ready?
Father, every challenge, every spirit, every will that is disturbing your life
I command them out, in the name of Jesus!
You demon, come out, in Jesus' name!
I command that devil, that will that is not of God, the will that is not of Jesus - I say to that will:
let the will of God be done!
That challenges in your life - command them out!
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I have destroyed her life.
I'm working to waste it, I want to destroy her family.
I'm her spiritual husband.
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
I want to marry her.
We are many.
Number one?
Spiritual husband.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
I want to destroy her marriage.
I don't want her to be married.
In the name of Jesus Christ!
I speak to every sickness in your life
and I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus.
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus.
Every demon in your life, I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus.
Leave them in the name of Jesus!
In the name of Jesus!
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
[Leave her alone.]
She must be put to shame.
She says she wants to marry...
She must come out.
I have scattered her marriage.
The SCOAN Mass Prayer
I am the spiritual husband.
I have destroyed, I don't want her to get married.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Vomiting Poisonous Substances
In the name of Jesus Christ!
Viewers all over the world, ask God to give you enablement,
to give you grace to forgive those who sin against you.
Lord Jesus, give me grace – grace enough!
In Jesus Christ's name!
Viewers, listen to the voice of God.
Whatever demon in your life, I speak to them and I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Let there be light!
Every sickness in your life, in your bones, in your tendons, in your kidneys,
in your liver, in your blood, in your bones -
right now, I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
You sickness, you disease, you affliction – leave my people!
At the name, Jesus, every tongue shall confess, every knee shall bow.
I say, you demon – you are synonymous with affliction!
You are synonymous with sickness!
Leave my people!
In the name of Jesus!